[{"answer": "It sounded like a jet plane being on top of your roof and all your windows getting busted out.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What did it feel like to you?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Right now, there was a lady that picked us up from the rescue center and he took us to her house last night.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "So what are you doing for accommodation?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I feel very lucky because we're alive.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "And despite how awful the state of your home is, do you feel lucky, Ronna, given that other people were killed last night and so much devastation?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I would say that it's been a challenging week, but in many ways, a week that I've enjoyed because I think that when a press secretary goes to the briefing room and there's a lot of intensity in the room and a lot of news, that, you know, it's inspiring reporters to ask hard questions.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Would you say this has been your toughest week personally in your job?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "That's part of the investigation led by the FBI that the president ordered immediately in the aftermath of the attacks in Benghazi.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Can you comment on that?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I dismiss the premise, the idea that these were scandals.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Let me ask you, first of all, did you ever think you'd have to deal with three scandals like this at the same time?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "I very strongly believe, as does the president, in the need for the press to be able to pursue investigative journalism freely.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Are you outraged by that as a journalist?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not sure, again, you're concocting scandals here that don't exist, especially with regard to the Benghazi affair that was contrived by Republicans and I think has fallen apart largely this week.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Do you accept that and just on a general picture, how are you going to move on now and restore perhaps faith that some Americans have lost this week in your openness and honesty?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "That's what it looks like so far.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Is the belief of the investigators and the police now that the more they dig into this, the more likely it is that he just had these three women, that was what he concentrated on, that there may not be other crimes outside of that?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, we all want that and there has been talk a couple of times that they're going to speak, they're going to speak, they're going to say something, and it never happened.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Are they likely to speak in public any time soon, do you think?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, they haven't questioned him in the last several days, although he is still in the same isolation in the cell, being watched 24/7 by the sheriff's department.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "And is Ariel Castro still cooperating with police, as he has been?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "There is a piece of that.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Is there a growing sense as there was in the first few days, maybe, that this should all have been solved a long time ago?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "The investigation -- well, really, I was watching your show last night, it's really from the defense side, it's damage control.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "First of all, looking at the Ariel Castro case since we last spoke, what is your assessment of where this investigation now is?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, from a legal perspective, the problem, if I was a defense attorney -- and the problem for the prosecution is the whole business of Mirandizing.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What would it mean legally, do you think?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "How you feeling?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Again, I'm not going to speak for the executive branch.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Should all the people who have had any involvement in targeting Tea Party groups just on the supposition that they're Tea Party activists -- should they all be fired?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Again, I'm not going to speak for the executive branch.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "If it turns out they were, if more e-mails come out and the State Department, for political reasons, were trying to remove the fact this may have been a terrorist attack, should heads roll at the State Department?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Should he?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not going to make news there.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "You haven't set a date for your wedding yet, have you?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I'm doing very well, thank you.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Penn, how are you doing?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I suppose so.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Feeling bullish?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "You know, this is one of those things that just breaks my heart.", "docId": "130516pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "As an American, somebody who pays a lot of taxes, I would imagine, like I do, how do you feel about the IRS turning all political, going off to people for their political believes?", "qSentId": 381}]